{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "On the fourth of next month he ___ (be) in prison for ten years.",
            "answer": "will have been",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have been\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: on the fourth of next month",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we reach Crewe we ___ (do) half of the journey.",
            "answer": "will have done",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have done\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: when we reach Crewe (means that by the time we are at Crewe)",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "At this rate you ___ (break) all the wine glasses by the end of the month.",
            "answer": "will have broken",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have broken\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word:  by the end of the month",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "If we don't hurry the sun ___ (rise) before we reach the top.",
            "answer": "will have risen",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have risen\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word:  before",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "A: I'm going to Hyde Park to hear the people making speeches.\nB: You'll be too late. By the time you get there they ___ (finish) their speeches and everybody have gone home.",
            "answer": "will have finished",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have finished\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the time\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "By midnight he ___ (be) unconscious for forty-eight hours.",
            "answer": "will have been",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have been\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by midnight",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "By the end of the month 5,000 people ___ (see) this exhibition.",
            "answer": "will have seen",
            "explain": " Correct.\n\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the end of the month",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "By next April I ___ (pay) Â£3,000 in income tax.",
            "answer": "will have paid",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have paid\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by next April",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I suppose that when I come back in ten years' time all these old houses ___ (be) pulled down.",
            "answer": "will have been",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have been\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: when I come back in ten years' time (means that by the time of ten years from now)",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "On 21 October they ___ (be) married for twenty-five years.",
            "answer": "will have been",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have been\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: on 21 October ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "7",
            "type": "4"
        }
    ]
}